Welcome.
This section is called providing great customer service.
So why is customer service so important to your business?
Every business is based upon customer.
The customer is the person who brings revenue and profitability into your business.
Now if you lose this customer, you are also losing the money or profitability that they brought in to you.
If you retain customer's, then you not only retain your business for a month, a year, but it could go on longer than that.
Think about the customer base that you could build upon from that one customer.
You could have word of mouth, advertising, it's just out there for you if your customer is happy with you.
So think of the value you will be receiving just from this one customer alone.
Again, the bottom line for any business is profitability.